deck1 = Deck.create(name: "Nighthawks")

card1 = Card.create(question: "What is a nighthawk's primary food source?", answer: "insects", deck: deck1)
card2 = Card.create(question: "True or false?  Nighthawks are closely related to hawks.", answer: "false", deck: deck1)
card3 = Card.create(question: "True or false?  Nighthawks make nests.", answer: "false", deck: deck1)
card4 = Card.create(question: "Where do Common Nighthawks spend the winter?", answer: "South America", deck: deck1)
card5 = Card.create(question: "True or false?  Bullbat is another name for the Common Nighthawk.", answer: "true", deck: deck1)

deck2 = Deck.create(name: "Otters")

card6 = Card.create(question: "What is an otter's primary food source?", answer: "fish", deck: deck2)
card7 = Card.create(question: "True or false?  Otters spend the majority of their time on land.", answer: "true", deck: deck2)
card8 = Card.create(question: "How many species of otters are there?", answer: "13", deck: deck2)
card9 = Card.create(question: "True or false? Otters are native to Australia?", answer: "false", deck: deck2)
card10 = Card.create(question: "True or false? Otters make and use tools.", answer: "true", deck: deck2)
card11 = Card.create(question: "In years, what is the average life span of an otter in the wild?", answer: "10", deck: deck2)

user1 = User.create(username: "mjcataldi", password: "password")
user2 = User.create(username: "jcce", password: "password")
user3 = User.create(username: "rrpatel25", password: "password")

round1 = Round.create(user: user1, deck: deck1)
round2 = Round.create(user: user1, deck: deck2)
round3 = Round.create(user: user2, deck: deck1)
# round4 = Round.create(user: user2, deck: deck2)
# round5 = Round.create(user: user3, deck: deck1)
# round6 = Round.create(user: user3, deck: deck2)

Guess.create(round: round1, card: card1, correct?: true)
Guess.create(round: round1, card: card2, correct?: false)
Guess.create(round: round1, card: card3, correct?: 1)
Guess.create(round: round1, card: card4, correct?: 0)
Guess.create(round: round1, card: card5, correct?: 1)

Guess.create(round: round2, card: card1, correct?: 1)
Guess.create(round: round2, card: card2, correct?: 0)
Guess.create(round: round2, card: card3, correct?: 1)
Guess.create(round: round2, card: card4, correct?: 0)
Guess.create(round: round2, card: card5, correct?: 1)

Guess.create(round: round3, card: card1, correct?: 1)
Guess.create(round: round3, card: card2, correct?: 0)
Guess.create(round: round3, card: card3, correct?: 1)
Guess.create(round: round3, card: card4, correct?: 0)
Guess.create(round: round3, card: card5, correct?: 1)
